Michael de Oliveira

Software Architect | IT Manager | Technology Manager

Brazillian, 33 Living in Blumenau / SC +55 (47) 99108.3796 https://www.linkedin.com/in/michael-oliveira-57167940/ michael.etec@gmail.com



Summary

I've been working with software development for 13 years. I hold a MBA in software Architecture and also several technical certifications that are relevant for the field. I've been working also largely with team management in large projects development. I additionally have experience being a consultant for IT companies inf offering a strategic and differentiated service through a digital transformation using technologies such as IA, Blockchain, IoT, among others.

Education

- Technologist: Desenvolvimento de Sistemas Comerciais, Federal Institutede tecnologia de São Paulo
- Higher education: *Sistemas de informação*, Cruzeiro do Sul Brazil
- Specialization: Web Development for Web Application, Furb Reginal University of Blumenau Brazil
- Master of Business: Software Architecture, IGTI

Certifications

- MCSA: Web Applications
- MCPS: Microsoft Certified Professional
- MS: Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3
- MCSD: App Builder 2017
- MCSD: Web Applications

Work history

- 2015 a 2019:
 - O Systems Analyst: AMcom Sistemas de Informação -SC, Brazil.
 - o Software Architect: AMcom Sistemas de Informação SC, Brazil.
 - o <u>Technology and Innovation Manager</u>: AMcom Sistemas de Informação SC, Brazil.
- 2009 a 2014:
 - O Systems Analyst: Cetil Sistemas SC, Brazil.
 - o Systems Analyst: Governança Brasil SC, Brazil.
- 2005 a 2008:
 - o Professor: Centro Paula Souza SP, Brazil.
 - o Consultant: Independent SP, Brazil.

Skills

Innovator / Dynamism/ Comunication / Agility/ Strategic Vision / Leadership/ People Management/ Decision Making / Resiliency / OKR Management/ Strategic planning/ Digital transformation/ Self-motivation / Proactivity/ Focus/ Conflict management/ Self-directed / Goal-Oriented.

Languages

- English: Fluent
- · Portuguese: Native speaker